Guide to the Elizabeth Page Harris Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Organizations and Causes, 1916-1968; Series IV; 6.5' (16 boxes)
  - American Friends Service Committee
    - Foreign Service Section
      - International Centers Subcommittee
        - Letters: Brinton, Howard and Anna, 1953-1954 (Box 75, Folder 1617)
        - Letters: Burt, Lucy M., 1948-1955 (Box 75, Folder 1618)
        - Letters: Chakravarty, Anna, 1951 (Box 75, Folder 1619)
        - Letters: Keene, Calvin, 1949 (Box 75, Folder 1620)
        - Letters: Kruse, Cornelius, 1951 (Box 75, Folder 1621)
        - Letters: Lapwood, Ralph and Nancy, 1951-1952 (Box 75, Folder 1622)
        - Letters: Silcock, Harry T., 1948 (Box 75, Folder 1623)
        - Letters: Steere, Douglas and Dorothy, 1947-1955 (Box 75, Folder 1624-1627)
        - Letters: Vail, James and Ruth, 1951 (Box 75, Folder 1628)
        - Memoranda and reports, 1947-1955 (Box 75, Folder 1629)
        - Minutes, 1947-1955 (Box 75, Folder 1630-1632)
        - Newsletters, 1948-1953 (Box 75, Folder 1633)
        - Quaker International Affairs Representatives, 1954-1955 (Box 75, Folder 1634-1635)
        - Reports, evaluations, etc., 1939-1959 (Box 76, Folder 1636)
        - European trip: Certificate of identity, 1946 (Box 76, Folder 1637)
        - European trip: Handbooks, 1944-1946, undated (Box 76, Folder 1638-1639)
        - European trip: Letters, 1946 (Box 76, Folder 1640)
        - European trip: Notebooks, 1946 (Box 76, Folder 1641-1643)
        - European trip: Notes, 1946 (Box 76, Folder 1644)
        - European trip: Papers, 1946 (Box 76, Folder 1645)
        - European trip: Survey notebook, 1946 (Box 76, Folder 1646)
      - Planning Committee, 1947 (Box 76, Folder 1647)
      - Quaker International Volunteer Service, 1948, 1953, undated (Box 76, Folder 1648)
      - Refugee Services
        - Bulletins, 1941-1943 (Box 76, Folder 1649)
        - Notes, undated (Box 76, Folder 1650)
        - Papers, 1939-1966, undated (Box 77, Folder 1651)
        - Worksheets on Zora Maria Kussevich, 1941 (Box 77, Folder 1652)
      - Relief Services
        - Bulletins, 1943-1944 (Box 77, Folder 1653)
        - Bulletins on China, 1942-1944 (Box 77, Folder 1654)
        - Bulletins on England, 1942-1943 (Box 77, Folder 1655)
        - Bulletins on France, 1940-1945 (Box 77, Folder 1656)
        - Pamphlets, 1947 (Box 77, Folder 1657)
      - School Affiliation Service, 1948-1955, undated (Box 77, Folder 1658-1659)
      - Subcommittee on Social and Technical Assistance, 1952-1955 (Box 77, Folder 1660-1661)
    - Peace Section
      - Bibliography, 1943 (Box 77, Folder 1662)
      - Meetings, 1940-1948 (Box 77, Folder 1663)
      - Papers, 1931-1966, undated (Box 77, Folder 1664)
      - Visits to Moscow, 1951, 1955 (Box 77, Folder 1665)
  - Society of Friends
    - Bennington Monthly Meeting
      - Broadcast, 1965 (Box 77, Folder 1666)
      - Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 77, Folder 1667)
      - Minutes, 1967-1968 (Box 77, Folder 1668)
      - Papers, 1963-1967, undated (Box 77, Folder 1669)
      - Treasurer's reports, 1965-1968 (Box 77, Folder 1670)
    - Friends Committee on National Legislation
      - Correspondence, 1948-1966 (Box 77, Folder 1671)
      - Papers, 1947-1966 (Box 77, Folder 1672)
      - Washington newsletters, 1947-1968 (Box 77, Folder 1673-1674)
    - Friends General Conference
      - Correspondence, 1948-1950 (Box 77, Folder 1675)
      - Papers, 1942-1965, undated (Box 77, Folder 1676)
    - Friends Intelligencer, 1941-1966 (Box 77, Folder 1677-1678)
      - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 77, Folder 1679)
    - Friends Retirement Association, 1961-1967, undated (Box 77, Folder 1680)
    - Friends Service Council, 1947-1948 (Box 78, Folder 1681)
    - Friends, Society of
      - Correspondence, 1941-1966 (Box 78, Folder 1682)
      - Miscellaneous papers, 1941-1966, undated (Box 78, Folder 1683)
      - Miscellaneous publications, 1942-1967, undated (Box 78, Folder 1684)
    - Friends World Committee for Consultation
      - Calendars, 1943-1963 (Box 78, Folder 1685)
      - Correspondence, 1947-1967 (Box 78, Folder 1686)
      - Directory, 1943 (Box 78, Folder 1687)
      - Friends World News, 1942-1963 (Box 78, Folder 1688)
      - Minutes, 1945-1946 (Box 78, Folder 1689)
    - New England Yearly Meeting, 1967 (Box 78, Folder 1690)
    - The Nor'wester, 1966-1967 (Box 78, Folder 1691)
    - Orange Grove Monthly Meeting
      - Circular letters, 1942-1964 (Box 78, Folder 1692)
      - Correspondence, 1941-1967, undated (Box 78, Folder 1693-1695)
      - Directories, 1947-1967, undated (Box 78, Folder 1696-1697)
      - Orange Grove Record, 1945-1967 (Box 78, Folder 1698-1699)
      - Papers, 1942-1967, undated (Box 78, Folder 1700)
      - "A Wartime Opportunity", undated (Box 78, Folder 1701)
    - Pacific Ackworth Friends School
      - Correspondence and papers, 1961-1963, undated (Box 78, Folder 1702)
      - Newsletters, 1944-1946 (Box 78, Folder 1703)
      - Correspondence, 1963, 1966 (Box 78, Folder 1704)
      - Friends Bulletin, 1942-1944 (Box 78, Folder 1705)
      - Friends Bulletin, 1947-1963 (Box 79, Folder 1706)
    - Pacific Oaks Friends School
      - Correspondence, 1948-1954 (Box 79, Folder 1707)
      - Papers, 1946-1965, undated (Box 79, Folder 1708)
    - Pendle Hill Center
      - Papers, 1950-1967 (Box 79, Folder 1709)
      - Pendle Hill Bulletin, 1942-1965 (Box 79, Folder 1710)
    - Philadelphia Yearly Meeting
      - Book of Meetings, 1940 (Box 79, Folder 1711)
      - Correspondence and papers, 1942-1952 (Box 79, Folder 1712)
      - The Messenger, 1942 (Box 79, Folder 1713)
      - News Notes, 1942-1945 (Box 79, Folder 1714)
      - Reports of Civil Liberties Committee, 1957 (Box 79, Folder 1715)
      - Reports of committees, 1942, 1950 (Box 79, Folder 1716)
    - Rural Life Association
      - Correspondence, 1948, 1952 (Box 79, Folder 1717)
      - Papers, 1948, undated (Box 79, Folder 1718)
      - The Rural Mailbox, 1948-1949 (Box 79, Folder 1719)
    - Neo-Sublime: bibliography and notes re: historical development, Vida's use of Horace and influence on later writers, Boileau's L'Art Poétique, English writers, quarrel between Pope and Dennis, attitudes toward genius versus correctness and imitation, 1947 (Box 79, Folder 1720)
    - Vermont Friends, 1948-1949, undated (Box 79, Folder 1721-1722)
    - Wider Quaker Fellowship, 1945-1952, undated (Box 79, Folder 1723)
  - Japanese Relocation
    - Correspondence, 1942-1943 June (Box 79, Folder 1724-1732)
    - Correspondence, 1943 July-1946 (Box 80, Folder 1733-1735)
    - American Friends Service Committee, Pacific Coast Branch
      - Interracial Relations Committee, 1942-1943 (Box 80, Folder 1736)
      - Japanese-American Relations Committee, 1942-1946 (Box 80, Folder 1737-1738)
      - Papers, undated (Box 80, Folder 1739)
    - Committee on American Principles and Fair Play, 1942-1945, undated (Box 80, Folder 1740)
    - Gila News-Courier, 1942-1943 June (Box 80, Folder 1741-1748)
    - Heart Mountain Sentinel, 1943-1944 (Box 80, Folder 1749)
    - JACL Reporter, 1945 (Box 80, Folder 1750)
    - Magazine articles, 1942 (Box 80, Folder 1751-1752)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1942-1944 (Box 80, Folder 1753)
    - Notes, undated (Box 80, Folder 1754)
    - Pacific Citizen, 1942 - 1943 January (Box 80, Folder 1755-1757)
    - Pacific Citizen, 1944 August - 1945 November (Box 81, Folder 1758-1770)
    - Pamphlets, 1942-1945, undated (Box 81, Folder 1771-1772)
    - Papers, 1941-1944, undated (Box 81, Folder 1773-1774)
    - Poetry, undated (Box 81, Folder 1775)
    - Poston "Press Bulletin", 1942 May - September (Box 81, Folder 1776-1779)
    - Poston "Press Bulletin", 1942 October - November (Box 82, Folder 1780-1782)
    - Trek, 1943 June (Box 82, Folder 1783)
    - Tulare News, 1942 (Box 82, Folder 1784-1787)
    - War Relocation Authority, 1942-1943 (Box 82, Folder 1788)
  - Other Causes
    - Action for a Federated World, 1944 (Box 82, Folder 1789)
    - American Civil Leberties Union, 1935-1958, undated (Box 82, Folder 1790-1792)
    - American Council on Soviet Relations, 1941, undated (Box 82, Folder 1793)
    - Anti-Communism: Plain Talk, 1946 (Box 82, Folder 1794)
    - Atlantic Union Committee, 1949, undated (Box 82, Folder 1795)
    - Barradas League, 1943, 1946 (Box 82, Folder 1796)
    - Children
      - Hazel Hurst Foundation, 1940-1942 (Box 82, Folder 1797)
      - Miscellaneous causes, 1941-1942, undated (Box 82, Folder 1798)
      - New England Kurn Hattin Homes, 1954-1967, undated (Box 82, Folder 1799)
    - China relief, 1939-1951, undated (Box 82, Folder 1800)
    - Civil rights, 1942-1966, undated (Box 82, Folder 1801)
      - CORE, 1952-1967 (Box 82, Folder 1802)
      - NAACP, 1944-1968 (Box 82, Folder 1803)
      - National Sharecroppers Fund, Inc., 1949, 1962 (Box 82, Folder 1804)
      - Odell Waller case, 1942 (Box 82, Folder 1805)
    - Commission to Study the Organization, of Peace, 1941-1943, undated (Box 82, Folder 1806-1807)
    - The Committee for the Defense of Public Education, 1941 (Box 82, Folder 1808)
    - Conscientious objectors
      - Central Committee for Conscientious Objectors, 1949-1966, undated (Box 83, Folder 1809)
      - National Council Against, Conscription, 1947-1951 (Box 83, Folder 1810)
      - National Service Board for Religious Objectors, 1943-1968 (Box 83, Folder 1811-1812)
      - Pacifica Views, 1943-1945 (Box 83, Folder 1813-1816)
      - Papers, 1942-1952, undated (Box 83, Folder 1817)
    - End Poverty in California, 1934 (Box 83, Folder 1818)
    - Federal Union, Inc.
      - Correspondence, 1939-1963 (Box 83, Folder 1819-1830)
      - Debate between Elizabeth Page and Rupert Hughes, 1940 (Box 83, Folder 1831)
      - Draft of article by Elizabeth page, 1940 (Box 83, Folder 1832)
      - Editorial comment, 1939 (Box 83, Folder 1833)
      - Federal Union News, 1940 (Box 83, Folder 1834)
      - Federal Union World, 1940-1943 (Box 83, Folder 1835-1836)
      - Headquarters bulletins, 1940 (Box 84, Folder 1837)
      - National office, 1939-1940 (Box 84, Folder 1838)
      - Newspaper clippings and reprints, 1939-1940, undated (Box 84, Folder 1839)
      - Notes, 1940 (Box 84, Folder 1840)
      - Pamphlets and miscellaneous, 1939-1944, undated (Box 84, Folder 1841)
      - Pasadena Chapter, 1940, undated (Box 84, Folder 1842)
      - Radio addresses, 1940, undated (Box 84, Folder 1843)
      - Regional newsletters, 1940-1941 (Box 84, Folder 1844)
    - Federal World Government, Inc., 1944-1945 (Box 84, Folder 1845)
    - Fellowship of Reconciliation
      - Correspondence, 1920-1950 (Box 84, Folder 1846)
      - General letters to membership, 1932-1967 (Box 84, Folder 1847)
      - Newsletters and policy statements, 1939-1968 (Box 84, Folder 1848-1849)
      - Papers, 1920-1966, undated (Box 84, Folder 1850-1851)
      - World War I, 1916-1917, undated (Box 84, Folder 1852)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1932-1954 (Box 84, Folder 1853)
    - League of Nations, 1929, undated (Box 84, Folder 1854)
    - McCarthyism: The Progressive, 1954 (Box 84, Folder 1855)
    - Miscellaneous causes, 1917-1963, undated (Box 84, Folder 1856-1857)
    - Pacifism
      - Federal Council of Churches, 1950, undated (Box 84, Folder 1858)
      - League of Industrial Democracy, 1931 (Box 84, Folder 1859)
      - Papers, 1929-1963, undated (Box 84, Folder 1860)
    - Post War World Council, 1943-1955 (Box 85, Folder 1861-1862)
    - "A Reform Movement That Failed", undated (Box 85, Folder 1863)
    - Relief for Americans in Philippines, 1942-1945 (Box 85, Folder 1864-1866)
    - Scottsboro Case, 1931-1932 (Box 85, Folder 1867)
    - Socialist Party U.S.A., 1939-1954 (Box 85, Folder 1868)
    - Socialist Party - Social Democratic Federation, 1958-1963 (Box 85, Folder 1869-1871)
    - Steel strike, 1949-1952 (Box 85, Folder 1872-1875)
    - United Nations
      - Fifth National Conference U.S. National Commission for UNESCO, 1955 (Box 85, Folder 1876-1877)
      - Papers, 1945-1964, undated (Box 85, Folder 1878)
      - United Nations Reporter, 1951 (Box 85, Folder 1879)
    - United States Committee for the Care of European Children
      - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 85, Folder 1880)
      - Notes and papers, 1940, undated (Box 85, Folder 1881)
      - Official forms, undated (Box 86, Folder 1882)
      - Press release, 1940 (Box 86, Folder 1883)
    - United World Federalists, 1949, 1965, undated
      - Vermont Branch, 1948, 1952 (Box 86, Folder 1885)
    - Workers Defense League, 1932-1946 (Box 86, Folder 1886)
    - The World Federation, Inc., 1942-1943 (Box 86, Folder 1887)
    - The World Tomorrow, 1923, 1927 (Box 86, Folder 1888)
- Writings, 1914-1971; Series V; 8.75' (22 boxes)
  Boxes 87-108 contain book length writings of Elizabeth Page Harris. The material is arranged alphabetically by title. Included are drafts of manuscripts of published works and unpublished writings together with movie scripts. Box 107, folders 2194-2195, contains book reviews by Elizabeth Page Harris and the series concludes with short stories and other writings.
  - "The Dark Command", 1939 (Box 87, Folder 1889-1892)
  - "Dawn's Early Light", 1940 (Box 87, Folder 1893-1902)
  - "Dawn's Early Light", 1940 (Box 87, Folder 1903-1909)
    - Notes, 1940 (Box 88, Folder 1910-1911)
  - Heritage and Challenge
    - Synopsis, undated (Box 88, Folder 1912)
    - Manuscript, 1948 (Box 88, Folder 1913-1914)
    - Manuscript, 1948 (Box 89, Folder 1915-1931)
    - Manuscript, Vol. I, 1966 (Box 89, Folder 1932-1937)
    - Manuscript, Vol. I, 1966 (Box 90, Folder 1938-1956)
    - Manuscript, Vol. I, 1966 (Box 91, Folder 1957-1958)
    - Manuscript, Vol. II, 1966 (Box 91, Folder 1959-1971)
    - Manuscript, Vol. II, 1966 (Box 92, Folder 1972-1982)
    - Charlottsville hearing, 1945 (Box 92, Folder 1983)
    - Correspondence, 1957-1971, undated (Box 92, Folder 1984)
    - Critique by Julian P. Boyd, 1965 (Box 92, Folder 1985)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1940-1969 (Box 92, Folder 1986)
    - Notes and papers, 1940-1976, undated (Box 92, Folder 1987)
    - Sound recordings, undated (Box 92, Folder 1988-1990)
    - Sound recordings, 1963-1967, undated (Box 93, Folder 1991-1998)
    - Theme, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 1999)
    - Microfilm, undated (Box 94, Folder 2000)
  - "The Howards of Virginia"
    See: Boxes 103-104, folders 2120-2129
  - "Immigration to the American Colonies, Between 1690 and 1765", 1914 (Box 95, Folder 2001-2002)
  - "In Camp and Tepee", undated (Box 95, Folder 2003-2007)
  - "The Trail of the Grafters" with Caroline Marsh Roe, Circa 1915 (Box 95, Folder 2008-2012)
  - The Tree of Liberty
    - Plot for "Jefferson's Men", undated (Box 96, Folder 2013)
    - Synopsis, undated (Box 96, Folder 2014)
    - Portions of early drafts, undated (Box 96, Folder 2015-2020)
    - Manuscript, 1935-1936 (Box 96, Folder 2021-2030)
    - Manuscript, 1936 (Box 97, Folder 2031-2044)
    - Manuscript: final revision, undated (Box 97, Folder 2045-2047)
    - Manuscript: final revision, undated (Box 98, Folder 2048-2053)
    - Manuscript: publisher's suggestions on final draft, undated (Box 98, Folder 2054-2063)
    - Manuscript: publisher's suggestions on final draft, undated (Box 99, Folder 2064-2071)
    - Acknowledgements, undated (Box 99, Folder 2072)
    - Announcements, 1939 (Box 99, Folder 2073)
    - Best seller lists, 1939 (Box 99, Folder 2074-2077)
    - Editions
      - American: The Literary Guild of America, Inc., 1939 (Box 99, Folder 2078)
      - Arabic, 1959 (Box 100, Folder 2079)
      - Hindi, 1968 (Box 100, Folder 2080)
      - Italian, 1946 (Box 101, Folder 2081)
      - Urdu, undated (Box 101, Folder 2082)
    - Farrar & Rinehart, Inc., 1940-1943, undated (Box 102, Folder 2083)
    - Jacket, 1939 (Box 102, Folder 2084)
    - The Literary Guild of America, Inc., 1939, 1952, undated (Box 102, Folder 2085)
    - Miscellaneous, 1935-1959, undated (Box 102, Folder 2086)
    - Newspaper clippings and writings on Jefferson, 1936-1969, undated (Box 102, Folder 2087)
    - Notes and comments, undated (Box 102, Folder 2088)
    - Notes for L. H. Christie, undated (Box 102, Folder 2089)
    - Notes for J. King Gordon, 1939, undated (Box 102, Folder 2090)
    - Notices, 1939 (Box 102, Folder 2091)
    - Publicity, 1939-1940 (Box 102, Folder 2092-2096)
    - Radio broadcast June 25, 1939 (Box 102, Folder 2097)
    - Reading notes, undated (Box 102, Folder 2098-2103)
    - Reading notes, undated (Box 103, Folder 2104-2107)
    - Review by Henry Steele Commager, 1939 (Box 103, Folder 2108)
    - Reviews, 1939 (Box 103, Folder 2109-2118)
    - Synopsis and outline, undated (Box 103, Folder 2119)
    - "The Howards of Virginia" (Box 103, Folder 2119)
      See also: Box 127, folder 2497
      - Script (Box 103, Folder 2120)
      - Suggested script changes, 1940 (Box 103, Folder 2121)
      - Script, 1940 (Box 104, Folder 2122)
      - Finances, 1939 (Box 104, Folder 2123)
      - Papers, 1955, undated (Box 104, Folder 2124)
      - Programs, 1940 (Box 104, Folder 2125)
      - Publicity, 1940 (Box 104, Folder 2126-2128)
      - Reviews, 1940 (Box 104, Folder 2129)
  - Wagons West
    - Outline and notes, 1927-1929 (Box 104, Folder 2130)
    - Draft manuscript and notes, 1927-1929 (Box 104, Folder 2131-2136)
    - Manuscript, 1927-1929 (Box 104, Folder 2137)
    - Manuscript, 1927-1929 (Box 105, Folder 2138-2141)
    - Galley proofs, 1930 (Box 105, Folder 2142)
    - Copy of diary of Henry W. Burton, 1849 undated (Box 105, Folder 2143)
    - Farrar & Rinehart, Inc.: catalogue, 1930 (Box 105, Folder 2144)
    - Jacket, 1930 (Box 105, Folder 2145)
    - Map, undated (Box 105, Folder 2146)
    - Notes, undated (Box 105, Folder 2147-2148)
    - Publicity, 1940 (Box 105, Folder 2149)
    - Reviews, 1930 (Box 105, Folder 2150-2151)
  - Wild Horses and Gold
    - Synopsis, 1932 (Box 105, Folder 2152-2153)
    - Manuscript, 1932 (Box 105, Folder 2154-2160)
    - Manuscript, 1932 (Box 106, Folder 2161)
    - Notes, 1933, undated (Box 106, Folder 2162-2163)
    - Copy of diary of Byron F. Wickwire 1897-1998, undated (Box 106, Folder 2164)
    - Copy of journal of Robert Campbell 1808-1851, undated (Box 106, Folder 2165)
    - Farrar & Rinehart, Inc.: catalogue, 1932 (Box 106, Folder 2166)
    - Map of the Edmonton Trail, 1932 (Box 106, Folder 2167)
    - Papers, 1930, 1932 (Box 106, Folder 2168)
    - Research notes, undated (Box 106, Folder 2169-2171)
    - Reviews, 1932 (Box 106, Folder 2172)
    - Reviews and newspaper clippings, 1932-1966 (Box 106, Folder 2173)
    - Suggested film treatment, 1936, undated (Box 106, Folder 2174-2175)
  - Wilderness Adventure
    - Synopsis, 1942 (Box 106, Folder 2176)
    - Manuscript, 1945 (Box 106, Folder 2177-2180)
    - Manuscript, 1946 (Box 107, Folder 2181-2192)
    - Reviews, 1946 (Box 107, Folder 2193)
  - Book reviews
    - Review of Meriwether Lewis of Lewis and Clark by Charles Morrow Wilson, 1934 (Box 107, Folder 2194)
    - Review of The Romance of Labrador by Sir Wildred Grenfell, 1934 (Box 107, Folder 2195)
  - Short stories and other writings
    - "Escape", 1933, undated (Box 107, Folder 2196-2198)
    - "An Experiment in Security", 1949 (Box 107, Folder 2199)
    - "It's the Unexpected", 1934, undated (Box 108, Folder 2200-2201)
    - Miscellaneous notes on writing, undated (Box 108, Folder 2202)
    - Miscellaneous writing exercises and diary entries, 1933 (Box 108, Folder 2203)
    - Miscellaneous writing notes, undated (Box 108, Folder 2204)
    - "Much Ado About Everything" and miscellaneous notes, Circa 1916 (Box 108, Folder 2205)
    - "Peace River" or "The Lost Frontier", undated (Box 108, Folder 2206)
    - "The Piper Is Paid: A Tale of the Alberta Woods?, undated (Box 108, Folder 2207-2208)
    - Poetry, undated (Box 108, Folder 2209)
    - "Private Piper", undated (Box 108, Folder 2210)
    - "Reversed Revenge", 1941, undated (Box 108, Folder 2211-2213)
    - "The Stripes of Corporal Preston", undated (Box 108, Folder 2214-2215)
    - "The Sunken Bell", undated (Box 108, Folder 2216)
    - "Sutton Notes" by Caroline Marsh Roe and Elizabeth Page, undated (Box 108, Folder 2217)
    - "The Tables Turned", undated (Box 108, Folder 2218)
    - "That Third Stripe", 1935, undated (Box 108, Folder 2219-2220)
    - Unidentified fragments, undated (Box 108, Folder 2221-2222)
- Printed Works, 1881-1959; Series VI; 3.0' (8 boxes)
  Series VI, PRINTED WORKS, contains just over four boxes of alphabetically arranged books and almost four boxes of alphabetically arranged shorter works.
  - Bacon, Marion. Mind Your Own Business, 1948 (Box 109, Folder 2223)
  - Betziner, Jason with W. S. Nye. I Fought with Geronimo, 1959 (Box 109, Folder 2224)
  - Bible, 1897 (Box 109, Folder 2225)
  - Bible, 1901 (Box 110, Folder 2226)
  - Brown, Anna Robertson. What is Worth While?, 1893 (Box 110, Folder 2227)
  - The Century Magazine, 1898 (Box 110, Folder 2228)
  - Coolidge, Dane and Mary Roberts Coolidge. The Last of the Seris, 1939 (Box 110, Folder 2229)
  - Daly, Augustin. A Night Off, 1897 (Box 110, Folder 2230)
  - Delly. Le Secret de Kou-Kou-noor, 1919 (Box 110, Folder 2231)
  - Drummond, Henry. The Greatest Thing in the World, undated (Box 111, Folder 2232)
  - Fitzgerald, Edward, trans. The Rubaiyat of Omar Khayyam, undated (Box 111, Folder 2233)
  - Harris, Burton. John Colter: His Years in the Rockies, 1952 (Box 111, Folder 2234)
  - Howells, William Dean. My Year in a Log Cabin, 1893 (Box 111, Folder 2235)
  - James, Marquis. The Cherokee Strip: An Oklahoma Boyhood, 1945 (Box 111, Folder 2236)
  - Keats, John. Isabella or The Pot of Basil, undated (Box 111, Folder 2237)
  - Lender, Charles Franklin. Down the Ohio with Clark, 1937 (Box 111, Folder 2238)
  - Mason, Charlotte. For Others, undated (Box 112, Folder 2239)
  - Pennell, Joseph. The Great New York, undated (Box 112, Folder 2240)
  - Rhys, Ernest. English Fairy Tales, undated (Box 112, Folder 2241)
  - Rocky and Selkirk Mountains, undated (Box 112, Folder 2242)
  - Shakespeare, William. Hamlet (French edition), undated (Box 112, Folder 2243)
  - Trenholm, Virginia Cole and Maurine Carley. The Shoshonis: Sentinels of the Rockies, 1945 (Box 112, Folder 2244)
  - Shorter works
    - Acting Plays and Entertainments, 1926 (Box 112, Folder 2245)
    - Annual Report of American Bureau for Medical Aid to China, Inc., 1967 (Box 112, Folder 2246)
    - Ausable Chasm, undated (Box 112, Folder 2247)
    - Bailey, Ralph Edward. Dark Eyes and Will Shakespeare, 1944 (Box 112, Folder 2248)
    - Better Filing, Indexing, Sorting, and Control Systems, 1937 (Box 112, Folder 2249)
    - The Blue Bird, 1913 (Box 113, Folder 2250)
    - Book catalogues, 1925, 1927 (Box 113, Folder 2251)
    - Browning, Robert. Saul and Other Poems, 1898 (Box 113, Folder 2252)
    - Budget Planning in a Social Work Case, 1919 (Box 113, Folder 2253)
    - Bulletin of the Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1909-1941 (Box 113, Folder 2254)
    - Bulletin of the Worcester Art Museum, 1917-1935 (Box 113, Folder 2255-2256)
    - Canham, Erwin D. The Christian Science Monitor, 1954 (Box 113, Folder 2257)
    - Child labor brochures, 1919-1920 (Box 113, Folder 2258)
    - Child nutrition pamphlets, 1919-1922 (Box 113, Folder 2259-2260)
    - Children's books, undated (Box 113, Folder 2261)
    - Circular of Information of The Wilkes-Barre Institute, 1915-1916 (Box 113, Folder 2262)
    - Civil Rights Crisis of 1957, 1958 (Box 113, Folder 2263)
    - The Common Glory, 1950 (Box 113, Folder 2264)
    - Construction of Boulder Dam, 1934 (Box 113, Folder 2265)
    - Crocheting pamphlets, undated (Box 113, Folder 2266-2267)
    - Daly, Augustin. A Night Off, 1897 (Box 113, Folder 2268)
    - Davie, Maurice R. and Samuel Koenig. The Refugees Are Now Americans, 1945 (Box 113, Folder 2269)